This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home.
I'm
so truly grateful.
I ran into you on that day so long ago.
We laughed every moment
with tears in our eyes.
Till we knew we weren't alone.
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way.
And with it I know we'll rise.
We'll be flying up high.
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you want to fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever!
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
I don't matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting
plans, we'll reach it.
We are home from the horizon
out on the edge of the world.
If there is a place that
I want to take you to?
Let's head for it then.
But as for the way we already know?
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice.
That can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated?
It crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I swear.
I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer together I'm
telling you in our path I trust that it
will lead us To another sea untarded
Cause now we are home On the horizon,
out on the edge of the world There
is a place that I want to take
you to Let's head forward then
But after the way we already know
We promised it long ago
Are you multiplying and
making animal sounds at me?
What the hell could have
happened to you all?
Come on, one of you's got to be real
Hey, Sanji!
Pudding! Chopper!
Carrot!
No, me!
Untie me now!
This one's talking like
she's really not me!
It is me!
I was looking everywhere for you, Luffy!
Who do you think you are, tying me up?
I'm really sorry, my bad.
I have to admit, though,
this is pretty bizarre.
She certainly does look like me.
Doesn't take much to realize
they're fake, though.
What with the animal sounds.
Thought you guys had multiplied
somehow. Not possible!
At least I don't think!
Gross!
Tell us what you know! Huh?
You've got to be hiding something from us.
You've been here the entire time, even when
that woman assaulted my friends and me.
I didn't see anything.
Don't lie to me.
Nami, someone was after you guys?
Yeah, actually, it was you, Luffy.
Really?
Well, technically, it was
a fake you, I suppose.
But we tried to escape
the forest with him.
That's confusing.
Then,
all of a sudden, that phony Luffy turned
into a gigantic woman, and she attacked us.
Let me go!
It's a scary tree!
The name's Barrel.
I'm not a tree.
Barrel?
A cute rabbit and a pretty girl.
What a charming little bunch you are.
When I see such bright
and beautiful faces,
I just want to dig in and scratch them up.
Nobie, no!
Stop!
Squirming won't help you, little lady.
He's probably lost in
the forest somewhere.
Claim attacked!
Are you Tia okay?
Uh-huh.
I am now.
Oh, thank you, Usopp.
Oh, you've done it now.
Be careful!
Leave this one to me!
A black claw! Please!
Now step aside, it's my turn here.
Reflection!
Carrot, no!
Are you okay?
Was Carrot's punch redirected
through the mirror just now?
Haven't figured it out yet, I have
the powers of the mirror-mirror-brute!
And just like a mirror reflects
any light that hits it,
if you throw a punch my way...
As you saw, I'll send
it right back to you.
Don't get close! Be careful!
Oh, I'm going to break that stupid mirror!
Take this, mirror world!
She disappeared, where is she?
Who wants to join her?
What happened to me?
I don't know how to get out.
What did you do to her?
You better let her go!
Don't get too close, Nami!
It's too late for that, sweetie.
Mama's already aware that you're all
here, so there's no use hiding from us.
Did you really think no
one noticed your arrival?
How hopelessly naive.
You might as well give up.
Mama gave everyone direct orders
to go after you, intruders!
That guy and those ones,
these fools, and even him.
Yes, we've all been given the
very same set of commands.
You don't need to kill
the Straw Hats not yet,
but don't let them near Sanji.
I want them to regret the fact that
they ever tried messing with me!
You can't outfox Mama.
She knows all that happens in her land.
Get to work, homies!
Don't let these dunces escape us!
Get away!
He got me!
Chopper, no!
Nami, just run!
There are too many of them!
It's over if all three of us get caught!
Don't forget they work for Big Mom!
We really shouldn't take this lightly!
Go find Luffy!
I'll hold them off in the meantime!
I understand!
I'll be right back!
Let's rumble!
Monster point!
Oh, take a gander at that.
A talking reindeer is fancy enough,
but it looks like he's got
even more tricks up his sleeve.
Mama will be delighted.
She's interested in collecting
all creatures of the world,
especially exotic types like you.
Wee! Wee! Wee!
Now catch them for Mama!
There's no use running, honey!
Get off!
Let me help!
Where are you?
Alone, I kept looking for you.
and running around until
darkness fell over the forest.
So that's what happened.
We're together now.
All righty then.
It's time to rescue Chopper
and Carrot from that lady.
Where are they?
Right here.
Everything that happened
was in this exact location.
But now no one's around anymore,
which is why I want answers.
You saw it all.
Where did Chopper go? And Carrot?
That creepy woman Barrel and all the weird
forest monsters didn't even mess with you.
That has to mean you're one of them.
Hmm, am I with them?
Well, I'm certainly not their enemy.
Oh, my throat might get posh, though.
But maybe I'd talk if you got
me some juice from over there.
It's apple juice all you ever think about.
But if you can tell us
something really good,
then sure, we'll bring your dumb drink.
Do you mean it?
Yeah, you keep talking about it.
I kind of want some, too.
By the way, you look pretty tough.
But what about you?
Yeah, I'm strong as hell.
What of it, weirdo?
My mistake.
Suppose you can't judge
a book by its cover.
Your reindeer buddy really took me
by surprise with how powerful he was.
He's probably still busy with all those
trees and flowers that attacked him, though.
If he's still standing, that is.
Once they've been given orders,
they're not gonna stop until
they accomplish their mission.
Yeah?
Well, if that's the case, then I have
to wonder why they stopped following me.
Hmm.
By the way, knocking them
around shuts them up, too.
But, uh, how can these
tree guys even move?
All of the residents here in Totoland
must pay the equivalent of one
month's worth of their soul to the
kingdom in exchange for their safety.
This happens every six months.
Like a tax?
Correct, but they pay with their lifespan.
Doing the math, the people lose
two months of their life each year,
and an entire year of their lives
every six years that they live here.
That's possible?
Lin-Lin, I mean, Big Mom has abilities
from consuming the soul soul fruit.
She's able to manipulate
anyone's soul as she pleases,
and she uses that power
to take away little
chunks of lifespan from
her loyal subjects.
They're faced with a difficult choice.
They can stay here in Toto
Land for a price or leave.
After gathering up everyone's souls,
she spreads them throughout the kingdom,
and all sorts of things become animated
and take on a life of their own.
We lovingly call these whimsical
little creatures homies around here.
This collection and distribution of
lifespan is operated by Linlin's, oh,
I mean, big mom's incarnations
that are made up of her own soul.
and that is the true
nature of toto land we
noticed that a lot of
unusual things were alive
when we arrived here so
does that explain the
talking crocodile and
human-like rabbit we saw
yeah that's correct she
gives animals human souls
that's incredible that means
them too actually that's a
whole different thing
Roulette used her ability to
turn normal animals into
decoy people to throw you off.
Oh, also, the souls can't be put
into corpses or other people.
Why didn't you tell us?
You've been watching this whole time!
I didn't want to get myself
involved, okay? Jeez!
That's a crappy answer.
Why are you buried here anyway?
Yeah, what she said!
Tell us who you are!
Say it, or else no juice for you!
Okay, I'll tell you everything.
Get off of me!
Don't hurt me.
A very long time ago, Big Mom and I were
once, er, rather, Charlotte Lin-Lin and I
were once
married as husband and wife. Okay!
Uh, a sweet three general?
Why is he here?
Hey, Straw Hat.
I'm going to make you regret.
Ever-stepping foot on this island.
So you and Big Mom were...
Really, a married couple?
We even had two daughters together.
But sadly, after they were
born, she broke it off with me.
I mean, it's not like the homies
are my friends or anything.
More like I'm beneath their notice.
What now?
He's giant! Who's this guy?
Hold on there, sir.
What brings you to these woods?
Do you have a concern
with my presence here?
Of course not, sir.
You're always welcome in these parts.
Hey!
Oh!
Oh! Oh!
He's pulling him out of the ground!
Get your back, Nami!
No!
Oh!
Oh! Oh!
He's not a giant, his head's just big!
Have you gone mad?
You think we wouldn't notice that
you're spilling info to the enemy?
You insufferable fool! Wait!
Let's not be rash now, Cracker!
I wish to see my child!
Chiffon, even if it's only for a moment.
I heard she got married.
I only want to give her my blessing.
Have mercy on this old soul.
If I can talk to Linlin,
we can work something out.
I overheard a rumor that Lola ran away.
You don't understand.
I worry about my precious children.
Lola, huh?
She's your daughter?
One of my older sisters did the latter.
She ran off to see a while
back in search of a husband.
Of her choosing.
You said that she ran away.
Rekker let go of me.
I only want to see my
daughters is that so wrong.
I promise I'll never
ask for anything else.
Lola.
She must be...
Wow, Lola.
I didn't realize you went
to the New World already.
We didn't go there, you big silly.
We came from there in the first place.
My mama's a pirate just like me, you know?
Oh, that reminds me.
Here, you should take this.
It's my mama's Viva card.
A piece of paper? Whoa!
I hang on to that one.
One of the greatest pirates I've
ever met in my life was Lola's mom.
That'll come in handy someday.
Not just anybody gets one of those.
Everything makes sense now.
No way.
Lola told us that her mom was a pirate.
So it was Big Mom?
I can't believe it.
This guy, he's Lola's father.
Those two are back!
It's the bird and rabbit guy!
And it's flying now?
Randolph, hold!
Wait a sec, was that Haki?
Well, what else could it be?
They all screamed in terror.
And then withered away?
Randolf
Interrupting my entrance
and getting in the
way you must think you're
a real big shot now!
Well, Randolph?
My apologies. It was his idea.
That's a blatant lie!
This one's on you!
They can talk?
Please forgive us!
They're acting like he
holds a high position.
He's strong, that's for sure.
You know that Mama always likes
to stay ahead of the curve,
considering Straw Hat Luffy was
the man who beat Doflamingo.
She assumed Barrel would have a hard time,
So she sent me did my ears hear
that correctly brother dear?
She's back, huh!
If she had ordered me to kill
them, I would have off them by now.
Exactly right!
We, the Seducing Wood's team,
would have never allowed
a single assigned target!
to leave this forest alive!
Golly!
Not only did Barrel and Cranker
show up here, but King Palme, too!
Wow!
It's hard to believe they're all
in the woods at the same time!
That's just dandy.
But we have little time for your games.
By tomorrow at noon,
the Vinsmoke siblings will be
arriving at the Whole Cake Shit?
making time a precious commodity.
Forming a family connection
with the Vinsmooks has been
a long-awaited goal that
Mama's been working towards.
She'll finally obtain Germa Double Six's
military might and scientific expertise.
I realize that.
He turned into animals!
Hold up.
How can that tree talk?
What did you just call me?
Tell me, can a tree do this, huh?
Luffy! Luffy!
Luffy, come and send us free!
She caught Chopper, too?
What happened, you guys?
How did you get in there?
She trapped us both in this mirror world.
She can use a tricky
ability, so be careful.
How do you like that, Brother Cracker?
I've got these fools
right where I want them.
By the scruff of their neck.
No, what happened?
Answer me! Are you okay?
We're fine.
It didn't hurt us.
It was only the mirror that broke.
Nothing bad happened to us
here in the mirror world.
What a relief.
I don't get it, but
that's good news at least.
Luffy, listen.
I'm wasting time.
First off, I'd better deal
with this loose-lipped fool.
What do you mean by that?
What are you going to do?
She said that I'm to kill you.
Can you reconsider, please?
We can still talk this through, Gregor.
Remember, I'm your stepdaughter after all.
In the past, yes, but not anymore.
Mama herself considers her 43
ex-husbands practically strangers.
To us, you're no longer
family and no longer blood.
Oh, how can you say that?
Telling me I'm no longer
related to my own daughters.
I can hardly bear it.
I promise, no funny business.
I only want to give
them my blessing, okay?
Ah!
Was that sympathy?
When you run into someone again
and again, you get attached!
Oh, thank you!
Really, thank you!
This is about to get ugly!
General Cracker's gonna stop that guy!
And maybe ask while he's at it!
Omasa, seize them so we can make
sure the job gets done right!
We should run!
It's not safe here!
Let's go!
You can leave the tower, Splay!
Don't let them escape!
What's your name, by the way?
You can just call me Bound!
About earlier, it sounded
like you know Lola.
I do, but...
Hold on a sec.
Here we go.
What have you got?
It's a present from my buddy Lola.
A piece of her mother's
beaver card, or so she said.
What?
I assume that's Big Mom.
What are you doing?
What's come over, all of you?
Even you, King Baum?
Tell me what's going on.
We can't proceed.
Sorry, mule.
Homies can't disoccupy her.
It's tree, son.
And why's that?
The sense mama's soul
and can't shrub it off.
This must be Big Mom's beaver card.
I had a hunch.
Just look at them.
Whoa, Luffy!
Are you okay?
Oh, no.
He's headed this way.
He grew worms? Damn it!
This guy sucks!
I am the Biscuit Knight Cracker, one
of Big Mom's Sweet Three Generals.
You shall learn to respect.
Thousand-armed cracker, Straw Hat.
By simply tapping like so,
I can grow another arm.
Tap twice and I get three.
I'm sure you get the picture. Huh?
However, that's not all.
No way!
Legs, too?
You couldn't even beat me
in your wildest dreams.
You fools will not interfere
with Mama's tea party.
Extra limbs won't help.
Now, second gear.
Hulk bust us all the arms you've got.
Come, come, get bullet.
And another one.
Come, come, Hulk whip.
Luffy, you can't turn
this into an Alto fight.
We need to get out of here.
Let's find Sanji so we can
leave this demented place.
Everything I do is all out.
Sorry, but it's the only way I know.